mulefactory.com 2019-07-02

# Privacy policy and data protection

## Privacy Policy

Mulefactory respects your privacy rights and protects all of your personal information provided by you. This document describes how our company treats and stores your personal information.

By using our site you agree that you have read this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to edit this document any time in the future so we encourge you to visit this site often. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy feel free to contact us any time via Live Help or e-mail.

We use your personal data only for making the required transactions. Every information of our customers will be saved and processed considering the legislation of the European Union.

There are several pages in our website that may direct you to other websites which do not operate under this Privacy Policy. These sites never get your personal informations unless they ask for your access on doing so. When you are at any of these external websites, this Privacy Policy no longer applies.

By personal information we mean any information that you share with us such as your e-mail address, name, phone number, payment method, order history, login location and other official documents you may share with us during our conversations. We don't always need you to send us official documents but when we do, it is strictly for security reasons. Our company collects personal information to verify the accuracy of your name in order to screen for fraud. We use your e-mail address only to contact you about your order status and to notify you about our news. No other data about you will be used, this also includes your phone number where we will never try to reach you. We do not share your personal data nor your e-mail address or in-game contact with any third parties without your explicit consent. We use technical and organisational safety precautions in order to protect your personal data from manipulation, loss, destruction or access to unauthorized people.

Our company stores all of your information on computers located in a controlled secure facility, which is protected from unauthorized physical or electronic access or use. We protect your privacy and integrity of the information collected by our employees for administrative protocols. Technical safeguards and physical security controls are designed to limit access, to prevent or decent unauthorized access and loss or manipulation of information under its control. Our method of electronic storage is 100% secure.

Mulefactory has **ZERO TOLERANCE** for any case of fraud regarding payments and access or acquisition customer information on their websites. We keep the rights to forward your verification such as telephone number or personal data to PayPal or Skrill for further review if any trouble occurs with your payment (attempt to charge back, unclear payment). Mulefactory aggressively prosecutes to the fullest extent of law against those perpetrators apprehended while conducting fraudulent activities on its website. We work with local, national and international fraud investigation agencies, and employ a variety of electronic and other means to discourage, detect and intercept fraudulent activities.

Our website uses cookies which means that we collect data whenever you visit our site. The collected data includes information about your browser, your device, location, ISP, date of access and websites which you reached us from and where you leave to. The data will be deleted as soon as they are no longer necessary to achieve their purpuse, which is usually statistical but also required to use certain functions, for example recognizing your computer when you return to our site. Cookies cannot implement any programs or transmit viruses to your computer. Cookies are stored on your computer as long as you are in the same browsing session or you empty your cookies cache. To use our website you have to accept that we are using cookies. The purpose of data collecting is provide full access to our services including Shopping Cart, Help Center or Affiliate System. By disabling cookies you will not be able to access these features.

We use your registered e-mail address to reach you out with Newsletters about twice a month and to bring your attention to our latest best selling or new products. Once you have registered you will automatically be subscribed for our Newsletter. If you do not wish to receive further Newsletters from us you can unsubscribe at any time. This option is available in your Profile once you have logged in.

If you would like to order in our shop, it is necessary for the conclusion of the contract that you give some of your personal data, which we need for the completion of your order. Your user account, including your payment informations, name and phone number can be deleted at any time and these informations cannot be accessed from that moment. To learn how to close your Mulefactory account, please see our [HelpCenter](https://www.mulefactory.com/helpcenter/)

Due to commercial and tax regulations, we are obliged to store some of your order details for a period of five years, it is to comply with legal obligations. To find out what data are we storing about you please contact us through Help Center and they will be shared with you. Mulefactory's site is not intended for or directed for people under the age of 18. Violating this restriction will result in immediate closure of the account and the transaction will be reversed to the original payment account.

8ms
